Guide to the School of Law Records, 1914-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
School of Law records 1914-Ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
Duke University. School of Law.
119.5 linear feet Extent: 73,600 Items
The School of Law dates its origins as far back as 1850. The school experienced many organizational changes and several temporary closures in its early years before re-establishing itself as the School of Law in 1904. This collection includes papers of deans of the law school in 1930 and continuing forward. Also included are materials related to the law school's publications, the Duke Bar Association, legal research centers, the law library, Richard Nixon's time as a student at the law school and general administrative files dating back to 1914.
UA.20.01.0001
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the University Archives to use this collection.
Collection is open for research.
For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
Provenance
The School of Law Records were received by the University Archives as a transfer starting in 1971.
Historical Note
The School of Law dates its origins as far back as 1850. The school experienced many organizational changes and several temporary closures in its early years. In 1904 it became the School of Law with the help of an endowment established by James Buchanan Duke and Benjamin Newton Duke. More details about the history of the law school can be found on their website here: http://www.law.duke.edu/history/timeline
Collection Overview
This collection includes papers of the deans of the School of Law starting in 1930. This material covers a wide range of information relating to the daily operations of the law school and includes: general correspondence, financial documents, annual reports, recruitment files, clerkship files, clippings, subject files, meeting minutes, development materials, and general office files. The collection also includes information about the various law school journals and publications edited and created by both students and faculty. Administrative files date back to 1914 and include: blank exams, financial documents, correspondence, placement bulletins, and other general files. Topics include legal education, Richard Nixon, administration, faculty, students, alumni, university presidents and administrators, the American Bar Association, the American Association of Law Schools, the school's Legal Aid Clinic, and law library.
Subject Headings
American Bar Association; Association of American Law Schools; Audiocassettes; Duke University -- Administration; Duke University -- Faculty; Duke University -- Presidents; Duke University -- Students; Duke University. School of Law; Duke University. School of Law -- Alumni and alumnae; Duke University. School of Law. Duke Bar Association; Duke University. School of Law -- Faculty; Duke University. School of Law. Legal Aid Clinic; Duke University. School of Law. Library; Legal education; Nixon, Richard M. (Richard Milhous), 1913-1994; Photographs; Press Clippings; Videotape
Separated Material
Photographs from the Dean A Kenneth Pye's records on the Allen Building Takeover have been transferred to the University Archives Photograph Collection.
A diskette from Dean Paul Carrington's records on the Duke Public Interest Law Consortium has been transferred to the University Archives Digital Media Collection. Contact the Electronic Records Archivist for more information.
Contents of Collection
- Deans Papers, 1929-1999, undated, 95 Linear Feet (63.5 boxes)
  Law School Dean's papers cover a wide range of topics relating to the management and operations of the law school. Some of the law school deans were faculty members before or after their time as dean, and there may be information from their time as faculty members within their papers. Further historical information about the deans of the law school is available here: http://www.law.duke.edu/history/deans
  - Dean Justin Miller, 1929-1934,undated
    Justin Miller became dean of the law school in 1930 and left in 1934.
    - A Correspondence, 1930-1934 (Box 1)
    - Admission to the Bar, 1930-1932, and undated (Box 1)
    - American Law Institute, 1932-1934, undated (Box 1)
    - American Law Institute, Joint Committee on Criminal Justice, 1929-1932, undated (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Announcements, undated (Box 1)
    - Applications for Positions, 1930-1934, undated (Box 1)
    - Associated Boards for Christian Colleges in china, 1933-1934 (Box 1)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1933-1934, undated (Box 1)
    - B Correspondence, 1931-1934 (Box 1)
    - Board of Trustees, Law School Committee, 1933 (Box 1)
    - Bolich, Bryan, 1932-1933 (Box 1)
    - Book Announcements, 1931, undated (Box 1)
    - Bruton, Paul W., 1932-1934, undated (Box 1)
    - Bryson, Judge T.D., 1932-1934 (Box 1)
    - C Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (3 folders) (Box 1)
    - Chamber of Commerce, 1932-1934 (Box 1)
    - Class Lists for Years 1931-1934 (Box 1)
    - Class Schedules, 1932-1934, undated (Box 1)
    - Clipping Service, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Commettees, 1932-1934 (Box 1)
    - Criminal Statistics, 1932-1933 (Box 1)
    - Current Research at Duke University, undated (Box 1)
    - Curriculum for years 1929-1935 and undated (Box 1)
    - D Correspondence, 1930-1934 (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Dean, Gordon, 1930-1933 (Box 1)
    - Duke Bar Association, 1932-1934, undated (2 folders) (Box 1)
    - Duke Bar Association Journal, 1933-1934, undated (Box 1)
    - E Correspondence, 1930-1934 (Box 1)
    - Employment Applications, 1932 (Box 1)
    - Examination Schedules, 1931-1934 (Box 1)
    - Examinations, 1931, undated (Box 1)
    - F Correspondence, 1930-1934 (Box 2)
    - Faculty Applications, 1929-1934 (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Faculty Club, 1932-1934 (Box 2)
    - Faculty Housing, 1931, undated (Box 2)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1930-1931, undated (Box 2)
    - Firm Announcements, 1932-1933 (Box 2)
    - Fuller, Warner, 1932-1933 (Box 2)
    - Furman University Law School Library, 1932-1934 (Box 2)
    - G Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - H Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (3 folders) (Box 2)
    - I Corresondence, 1930-1934, undated (Box 2)
    - Institute of International Relations, 1933-1934, undated (Box 2)
    - J Correspondence, 1930-1934 (Box 2)
    - K Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (Box 2)
    - Kirkwood, Marion, R., 1930-1931 (Box 2)
    - L Correspondence, 1930-1934 (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1933-1934, undated (Box 2)
    - Law Improvement Commission, 1931 (Box 2)
    - Law Library, 1930-1934, undated (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Law Review, 1931-1932, undated (Box 3)
    - Law School Administration, 1928-1933, undated (Box 3)
    - Law School Advisory Committee, 1932-1933, undated (Box 3)
    - Law School Bulletin, 1932-1934 (Box 3)
    - Law School Committee, 1930-1931, undated (Box 3)
    - Law School Cource Bulletin, undated (Box 3)
    - Law School Publicity, undated (Box 3)
    - Legal Aid Clinic, 1932-1934 (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Legal Aid Clinic Newsletter, 1932-1934 (Box 3)
    - Legal Biographical Collection, 1932-1933 (Box 3)
    - Legislation Department in the Law School, undated (Box 3)
    - Loan Fund, 1933 (Box 3)
    - M Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (3 folders) (Box 3)
    - McDermott, Malcolm, 1931-1934 (Box 3)
    - Maggs, Douglas B., 1933, undated (Box 3)
    - Markham, C.B., 1932-1933 (Box 3)
    - Memoranda to University President Few and Dr. Flowers, 1931-1934, undated (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - N Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (Box 3)
    - National Association of Legal Aid Organizations, 1931 (Box 3)
    - National Economic League, 1932-1933 (Box 3)
    - National Economy League, 1932-1933 (Box 3)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1933-1934, undated (Box 3)
    - O Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (Box 3)
    - Order of the Coif, 1932-1934, undated (Box 3)
    - P Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Parker School, 1930 (Box 4)
    - Photographs, 1933 (Box 4)
    - Q Correspondence, 1932-1934 (Box 4)
    - R Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Registration, undated (Box 4)
    - Rotary Club, 1931, undated (Box 4)
    - Report of Rules Committee, 1933 (Box 4)
    - S Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Sigma Nu Phi, 1931 (Box 4)
    - T Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - U Correspondence, 1930-1933, undated (Box 4)
    - V Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (Box 4)
    - W Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Washington Bicentennial Celebration, 1931-1932, undated (Box 4)
    - Whitford, William, 1931-1932 (Box 4)
    - Women's Student Government Association (Examining Board), 1934, undated (Box 4)
    - Y Correspondence, 1930-1934, undated (Box 4)
    - Z Correspondence, 1931 (Box 4)
  - Dean H.Claude Horack,1933-1948, undated
    H. Claude Horack served as dean of the law school from 1934-1947.
    - A Correspondence, 1933-1947, undated (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Absenses - Holidays, 1938-1939, undated (Box 5)
    - Accreditation, 1941 (Box 5)
    - Advertising, 1935-1939, undated (Box 5)
    - Advisory Committee on Recodification of North Carolina Statutes (N.C. Department of Justice), 1939 (Box 5)
    - Alabama Bar Association annual Meeting, 1935 (Box 5)
    - Alumni, 1942-1946, undated (Box 5)
    - Alumni Directory, 1935-1936, undated (Box 5)
    - Alumni Mailings, 1935-1936, undated (Box 5)
    - American Association of University Professors, 1934-1946, undated (Box 5)
    - American Bar Association, 1934-1947, undated (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - American Bar Association, Committee on Accreditation of Law Schools, 1939, undated (Box 5)
    - American Bar Association, Committee on Bar Examiniations in Relation to Approval of Law Schools, 1939, undated (Box 5)
    - American Bar Association, Legal Education Section District of Columbia Junior Colleges, 1932-1942, undated (Box 5)
    - American Bar Association, Meetings, 1935-1936 (Box 5)
    - American Bar Association, Section of Legal Education and Admissions to the Bar, 1940, undated (Box 5)
    - American Bar Association, State Council, 1935-1938 (Box 5)
    - American Council on Education and Higher Education and National Defense Publication, 1944-1945 (Box 5)
    - American Law Institute, 1934-1946, undated (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - American Society of Composers, Authors and Publishers (ASCAP), Nathan Burkan Memorial Competition, 1937-1946, undated (2 folders) (Box 5)
    - Andrews, Alexander B., 1934-1946 (3 folders) (Box 5)
    - Applicants for Teaching Positions on Law Faculty, 1936-1937 (Box 6)
    - Armed Forces Recruiting and Residence at Law School, 1942-1944, undated (Box 6)
    - Association of American Law Schools, 1934-1947, undated (7 folders) (Box 6)
    - Association of American Law Schools,Bar Admissions Committee, 1934-1937, undated (Box 6)
    - Association of American Law Schools, Curriculum Committee, 1938-1939, undated (Box 6)
    - B Correspondence, 1937-1947, undated (3 folders) (Box 6)
    - B.S. Degree in Law, 1942, undated (Box 6)
    - Beardsley, Charles A., 1939-1940 (Box 6)
    - Beating the Bounds, 1939, undated (Box 6)
    - Bennett, Rosanelle, 1938-1941 (Box 6)
    - Billig, Thomas, C., 1935-1936, undated (Box 6)
    - Blind Students, 1939 (Box 6)
    - Board of Deans, 1934 (Box 6)
    - Board of Legal Examiners, 1939-1945, undated (Box 6)
    - Bolich, Bryan B., 1934-1942, undated (Box 6)
    - Duke University Bookstore, 1934-1935 (Box 6)
    - Brenner, James E., 1936-1945 (Box 6)
    - Broughton, J. Melville, 1945 (Box 6)
    - Brown, Esther Lucille, 1938-1940 (Box 6)
    - Bruton, Paul, 1934-1935 (Box 6)
    - Bryson, Edwin C. 1936-1942 (Box 6)
    - Bryson, Thaddeus D., 1935-1944 (Box 6)
    - Bulletin Board, 1935 (Box 6)
    - Bureau of National Affairs, 1940 (Box 6)
    - C Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - California Bar Exam and Survey of Unapproved Law Schools in California, 1938, undated (Box 7)
    - Cannon, Edward, 1939-1946, undated (Box 7)
    - Cathcart, A. M. 1938-1939, undated (Box 7)
    - Cavers, David F., 1934-1945, undated (Box 7)
    - Catholic Legal Education, 1935-1937 (Box 7)
    - Centennial Symposium, 1937-1939, undated (Box 7)
    - Chadbourn, James H., 1935-1936 (Box 7)
    - Civil Service, 1941-1944, undated (Box 7)
    - Clark, Charles E., 1935-1941 (Box 7)
    - Class Lists, Schedules, Exam Schedules, 1933-1935, undated (Box 7)
    - Combined Course Arrangements for Years 1935-1941, undated (Box 7)
    - Commencement, 1947, undated (Box 7)
    - Committee on Aims and Objectives of Section of Legal Education, 1942-1946 (Box 7)
    - Committee on Cooperation Between Law Schools and the State Bar, 1937-1941, undated (Box 7)
    - Committee on Curriculum and Veterans' Problems, 1944-1946, undated (Box 7)
    - Contempt of Court Study, 1937 (Box 7)
    - Covington, Mary S., 1943-1945, undated (Box 7)
    - Crime Study Club, 1939-1940, undated (Box 7)
    - Curriculum Committee, 1933-1946, undated (Box 7)
    - Curriculum Committee, Wartime Changes, 1942-1945, undated (Box 7)
    - Currie, Brainerd, 1946, undated (Box 7)
    - D Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - Department of Justice Reports, 1939-1940 (Box 7)
    - Demuth, Laurence, 1940-1941 (Box 7)
    - Diploma Privlege Proposed North Carolina State Bill, 1939 (Box 7)
    - Donovan, Leisure, Newton and Lumbard, 1938-1940 (Box 7)
    - Duke Bar Association, 1933-1946, undated (folder 1 of 2) (Box 7)
    - Duke Bar Association, 1933-1946, undated (folder 2 of 2) (Box 8)
    - Duke Council for American Defense, 1941, undated (Box 8)
    - Duke Institute of International Relations, 1935-1938 (Box 8)
    - Duke University Day, 1934-1939, undated (Box 8)
    - Dunbar, Charles E. (Chas), 1940-1942 (Box 8)
    - Durham County Bar Association, Durham Junior Bar Association, 1937-1945, undated (Box 8)
    - E Correspondence, 1934-1946 (Box 8)
    - Emergency Law School Program due to World War II, 1942, undated (Box 8)
    - Enrollment Committee, 1941, undated (Box 8)
    - F Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Faculty Evening Meetings, 1936-1940, undated (Box 8)
    - Faculty Publications, 1925-1934, undated (Box 8)
    - Federal Bureau of Investigations, 1938-1946 (Box 8)
    - Federal Emergency Relief Administration, 1934-1935, undated (Box 8)
    - Fees, Special Students, undated (Box 8)
    - Few, William Preston, 1934-1940, undated (Box 8)
    - Fidelity Bank, Will Drafting Contest, 1935 (Box 8)
    - Fitzgerald, R.H. 1938-1940, undated (Box 8)
    - Flowers, Robert L., 1937-1947 (Box 8)
    - Foundation Press, 1946, undated (Box 8)
    - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference, 1935-1946, undated (Box 8)
    - Fuller, Lon L., 1935-1941, undated (Box 8)
    - Fuller, Warner, 1935-1936 (Box 8)
    - Furman University Law Library, 1934-1935 (Box 8)
    - G Correspondence, 1934-1947 (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Gambrell, E. Smythe, 1940 (Box 8)
    - Georgia, University of, Law School, Athens, GA., 1943, undated (Box 8)
    - Georgia, University System of, Clippings, 1941-1942 (Box 8)
    - Georgia, University System of, Correspondence, 1941-1943, undated (Box 8)
    - Georgia, University System of, Investigation by the committee Appointed by the Southern Association of colleges and Secondary Schools, 1941 (Box 8)
    - Georgia, University System of, Report on Charges of Political interference in the University System of Georgia, 1941 (Box 8)
    - Gillmore, Eugene, Allen, 1934-1941 (Box 8)
    - Goodrich, Edgar J., 1935-1941 (Box 8)
    - Goodrich, Herbert, F., 1938-1945, undated (Box 8)
    - Graduate Study Committee, 1935-1940, undated (Box 8)
    - H Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (2 folders) (Box 8)
    - Hanes Loan Fund, 1934-1946 (Box 8)
    - Hanft, Frank, 1938-1939 (Box 8)
    - Harno, Albert James, 1941-1945 (Box 8)
    - Harris, Rufus, 1939, undated (Box 9)
    - Harvard Club of North Carolina, 1937-1946, undated (Box 9)
    - Hoover, John Edgar, 1935-1946, undated (Box 9)
    - Horack, Benjamin, undated (Box 9)
    - Housing, 1946, undated (Box 9)
    - Hutchins, Fred, 1939 (Box 9)
    - I Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (Box 9)
    - Illinois Law Review, 1938-1940, undated (Box 9)
    - Institutes, 1942-1946, undated (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Inter-American Bar Association, 1946 (Box 9)
    - Iredell Scholarship Fund, 1937-1947, undated (Box 9)
    - J correspondence, 1934-1947 (Box 9)
    - Johnston, Gordon, 1941-1942 (Box 9)
    - Joint Committee on Intellectual Cooperation (with U.N.C.), 1936-1939 (Box 9)
    - Joint Law School, 1942-1945 (Box 9)
    - Jordan, Charles E., 1940-1947 (Box 9)
    - Journal of Higher Education, 1938-1945 (Box 9)
    - Junior Bar Association, 1938-1945, undated (Box 9)
    - Junior Colleges and American Bar Association Legal Education Standards, 1941-1942 (Box 9)
    - Juvenille Court of Durham, NC., 1935-1941 (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - K Correspondence, 1934-1946, undated (Box 9)
    - L Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (Box 9)
    - Lake, Beverly I., 1945 (Box 9)
    - Latty, Elvin R. Jack, 1937-1946 (Box 9)
    - Law Books Available from Individuals and Booksellers, 1938-1939, undated (Box 9)
    - Law Building, 1938, undated (Box 9)
    - Law School Committee, 1940-1946, undated (Box 9)
    - Law Faculty Meetings, 1934 (Box 9)
    - Law Library, 1934-1946, undated (Box 9)
    - Law Library Committee, 1937, undated (Box 9)
    - Law School Development, 1935, undated (Box 9)
    - Law School Expenditures by Code Number for 1934-1935 (Box 9)
    - Law Symposium, 1938-1939, undated (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Law and Contemporary Problems, 1934-1946, undated (Box 9)
    - Lawyers Co-operative Publishing Company, 1938-1946, undated (Box 10)
    - Legal Aid Clinic and Loan Fund, 1934-1947, undated (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Legal Education, 1938-1944, undated (Box 10)
    - Legislation in N.C. Manual Distribution Correspondence, 19396-1937, undated (Box 10)
    - Legislative Research and Drafting, 1934 (Box 10)
    - Linthicum Foundation Prize Competition, 1939 (Box 10)
    - Local Legislation Commission, 1938, undated (Box 10)
    - Loan Funds, 1938-1942, undated (Box 10)
    - Log Cabins for Law Students, 1937-1941, undated (Box 10)
    - Log Cabins Related News Clippings, 1938, undated (Box 10)
    - London, Henry, M, 1936-1939 (Box 10)
    - Louisiana State University Symposium, 1938, undated (Box 10)
    - Louisville, University of, Law School Inspection, 1935, undated (Box 10)
    - Lowndes, Charles, L.B., 1934-1945, undated (Box 10)
    - M Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (3 folders) (Box 10)
    - Maggs, Douglas B., 1935-1945, undated (Box 10)
    - McDermott, Malcolm, 1934-1947, undated (Box 10)
    - Markham, Charles B., 1935-1947, undated (Box 10)
    - Mattocks, James', Property Rights in Tide Water Area of North Carolina, undated (Box 10)
    - Miami, University of, Law School Inspection, 1938 (Box 10)
    - Miller, Charles, 1944-1945, undated (Box 10)
    - Miller, Justin, 1934-1935, undated (Box 10)
    - Missing Law Books, 1936, undated (Box 10)
    - Morse, Wayne, Arbitrator's Award Documents Regarding Controversy Between International Longshormen's And Warehousemen's Unions, 1939 (Box 10)
    - N Correspondence, 1933-1948, undated (folder 1 of 2) (Box 10)
    - N Correspondence, 1933-1948, undated (folder 2 of 2) (Box 11)
    - National Conference of Bar Examiners, 1941-1947, undated (Box 11)
    - National Conference of Law Students, 1940-1941, undated (Box 11)
    - National University, Junior College Inspection, 1942, undated (Box 11)
    - National Youth Administration, 1935-1942, undated (Box 11)
    - New York Firms, 1937-1945 (Box 11)
    - New York State University, 1941-1942 (Box 11)
    - News Releases, 1936-1945, undated (Box 11)
    - North Carolina, University of, at Chapel Hill Sesquicentennial, 1946 (Box 11)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, 1934-1947, undated (Box 11)
    - North Carolina State Bar, 1935-1945, undated (Box 11)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, Committee to Cooperate with the American Law Institute, 1935-1936 (Box 11)
    - North Carolina Bar Association, Special Committee on Rule Making Power of the Supreme court, 1938-1941, undated (Box 11)
    - North Carolina Bar Exam, 1934-1937, undated (Box 11)
    - North Carolina Board of Law Examiners, 1937-1939, undated (Box 11)
    - North Carolina college for Negroes, 1939-1946, undated (Box 11)
    - North Carolina State Conference, 1935-1936, undated (Box 11)
    - Northeastern University Survey, 1937-1941 (Box 11)
    - O Correspondence, 1934-1947 (Box 11)
    - Order of the Coif, 1930-1945, undated (Box 11)
    - Osborne Association, 1935 (Box 11)
    - Oxford Training in Law, 1931-1936, undated (Box 11)
    - P Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (3 folders) (Box 11)
    - Permanent court of International Justice, 1943-1945, undated (Box 11)
    - Phi Alpha Delta, 1946-1947 (Box 11)
    - Phi Beta Kapa, undated (Box 11)
    - Phi Delta Phi, 1940-1946 (Box 11)
    - Philbrick, Francis S., 1936-1937, undated (Box 11)
    - Pi Gamma Mu, 1934 (Box 11)
    - Placement of Law Students and Law Graduates Article, 1941, undated (Box 11)
    - Politics, 1940-1943, undated (Box 11)
    - Population and Lawyers, 1930-1931 (Box 11)
    - Positions Available, 1935-1947 (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Portraits, 1940 (Box 11)
    - Poteat, J Douglass, 1932-1946, undated (Box 11)
    - Pound, Roscoe Lecture, 1938-1939, undated (Box 11)
    - Practice court - Replies Concerning Manner of Conducting Court in a Number of Law Schools, 1937, undated (Box 11)
    - Pre-Legal Education, 1935-1942, undated (folder 1 of 2) (Box 11)
    - Pre-Legal Education, 1935-1942, undated (folder 2 of 2) (Box 12)
    - Presidents Report, 1934-1941, undated (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Privacy, Right of Report by James Mattocks, 1941 (Box 12)
    - Programs, 1935-1936 (Box 12)
    - Publicity, 1935-1937, undated (Box 12)
    - Q Correspondence, 1936-1942, undated (Box 12)
    - Questionaire on Student Study Practice, undated (Box 12)
    - R Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Racine, Charles W., 1941-1942 (Box 12)
    - Railroad Information and Itineraries, 1940-1944 (Box 12)
    - Recommendations, 1935-1938, undated (Box 12)
    - Refugee Lawyers, Placement of, 1939-1940 (Box 12)
    - Refresher Law Courses for Veterans, 1944-1945, undated (Box 12)
    - Research by Students, 1934-1937, undated (Box 12)
    - Research Council, 1934-1946, undated (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Rhine, Joseph Banks, 1938-1940 (Box 12)
    - Roalfe, William R. 1934-1946, undated (Box 12)
    - Ross Essay Contest, 1936-1938, undated (Box 12)
    - Royall, kenneth C., 1939 (Box 12)
    - Rush, Kenneth, 1935-1941, undated (Box 12)
    - S Correspondence, 1934-1947, undated (4 folders) (Box 12)
    - Sanders, Paul, 1935-1946, undated (2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Saint John's Law School Inspection, 1939-1940, undated (Box 12)
    - Salary Schedules, Law Schools, 1935 (Box 12)
    - Sawyer, O.G., 1934-1939 (Box 12)
    - Scheidt, Edward, 1938-1940 (Box 12)